Spaceship Earth is a documentary film directed by Matt Wolf.
In 1991 a group of countercultural visionaries built an enormous
replica of earth’s ecosystem called Biosphere 2.
When eight “biospherians” lived sealed inside, they faced
ecological calamities and cult accusations.
Their epic adventure is a cautionary tale but also a testament to
the power of small groups reimagining the world.
Himself, played by John Allen.
Himself, played by Tony Burgess.
Herself, played by Kathelin Gray.
Herself, played by Linda Leigh.
Himself, played by Mark Nelson.
Himself, played by Roy Walford.
Spaceship Earth is a 2020 American documentary film directed by Matt Wolf about the 1991 experiment that saw eight
individuals spend two years quarantined inside of a self-engineered replica of Earth's ecosystem, dubbed Biosphere 2.
The film premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 26, 2020, and
was released in the United States on May 8, 2020, by Neon.